Guide to the Stephen Henry Schneider Papers SC1053
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Conferences, Meetings, and Professional Travel, Series 6
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Item 3-4)
  - American Meteorological Society (AMS) meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Association of American Geographers (AAG) meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Bay Area Air quality Symposium (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Bren School Advisory Board Meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - California Climate Change Advisory Meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Climate Change Conference (Aspen), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Climate Change Conference (Seattle), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Climate Change event (Stegner Center, San Francisco), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Climate Change Research Conference, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Climate hearing (Fran Pavley/Global Green), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Conservation Strategy Fund, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Environment and Energy Vision Workshop, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - European Forum on Integrated Environmental Assessment (EFIEA) conference, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Global Climate and Energy Project (GCEP), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Global Environmental Action (GEA), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Haas Center, science outreach discussion, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Helen Caldicott (Nuclear Power and Global Warming conference), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - HBO documentary interview, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Institute for the Future, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) (Cairns), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), WG II (Merida), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 27-28)
  - Japan (Nissan), 2005 (Box 114, Item 29-30)
  - Jerry Brown dinner, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Johnson Foundation (Watermark Conference), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 32)
  - Jon Foley meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 33)
  - King County Climate Change Conference, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 34)
  - Knight Fellows Talk, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 35)
  - Meteorology Office (Exeter, U.K.), 2005 (Box 114, Item 36-37)
  - Monitor Project, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 38)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 114, Folder Folder)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 2005 (Box 114, Folder 40)
  - New York trip, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 41)
  - New Zealand lecture, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 42)
  - PIER conference, 2005 (Box 114, Item Folder)
  - The Prince of Wales’s Business and the Environment Programme, 2005 (Box 114, Item 45-46)
  - Princeton Project on National Security, 2005 (Box 115, Item 1-2)
  - Radio Hong Kong interview, 2005 (Box 115, Item 3)
  - Redefining Progress dinner, 2005 (Box 115, Item 4)
  - Robinson House Seminar Series, 2005 (Box 115, Item 5)
  - San Jose State University, Global Warming Seminar, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Sandia National Laboratories, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Sierra Club Foundation, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Stony Brook University, World Environmental Forum, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Swissnex/ World Environment Day, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Teacher’s Bioforum, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Unitarian Church, Hybrids Unplugged talk, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - UN World Environment Day, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - University of California, Berkeley; Breslaur Lecture, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - University of California, Berkeley; seminar, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - University of California, Berkeley; Science Communication and Media workshop, 2005 (Box 115, Item 16-18)
  - University of Michigan, strategic assessment, 2005 (Box 115, Item 19-20)
  - University of Southern California, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Ursinus College, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Folder 23-26 Yale-Aspen conference, 2005 (Box 115, Item 23-26)
  - Yale-Aspen, pre-conference reader, 2005 (Box 115, Item 27-28)
  - Yale conference - Global Warming: Looking Beyond Kyoto, 2005 (Box 115, Item 29)
  - Watermark - Wingspread conference, 2005 (Box 115, Item 30)
  - Weekend Today Show, 2005 (Box 115, Item 31)
  - Winslow Foundation, 2005 (Box 115, Item 32)
  - Wisdom for a Livable Planet, 2005 (Box 115, Item 33)
  - Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 115, Folder 34)
  - American Geophysical Union (AGU) meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Item 1-4)
  - Armand Neukerman’s Ranch talk, 2006 (Box 116, Item 5)
  - Assessing Katrina panel, 2006 (Box 116, Item 6)
  - CALPERS, 2006 (Box 116, Item 7)
  - Climate Change: Risks and Opportunities, 2006 (Box 116, Item 8)
  - Energy and Climate workshop, 2006 (Box 116, Item 9)
  - Global Business Network (GBN) interview, 2006 (Box 116, Item 10)
  - Google meetings, 2006 (Box 116, Item 11)
  - Imagining Environment conference, 2006 (Box 116, Item 12)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), WG II meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Item 13-14)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) WG II meeting (London), 2006 (Box 116, Item 15-16)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) (Cape Town), 2006 (Box 116, Item 17)
  - Ion Yadigaroglu, 2006 (Box 116, Item 18)
  - Jon Cooksey interview, 2006 (Box 116, Item 19)
  - Jonathon Weisgall meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Item 20)
  - League of Women Voters, discussion group (Box 116, Item 21)
  - Media talk, 2006 (Box 116, Item 22)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), regional meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Item 23)
  - National Research Council (NRC) meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Item 24-25)
  - Native Voices Fund, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Oakland Museum lecture, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - PG&E (Peter Darbee), 2006 (Box 116, Item 28-30)
  - Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Patient from Hell talk, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 32)
  - Penny Boston talk, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - Riley Dunlap visit, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 34)
  - Rosenfeld Symposium, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 35)
  - Sacramento talks, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 36)
  - San Francisco Chronicle interview with Jane Kay, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 37)
  - Seed Salon, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 38)
  - Senator Bingman, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 39)
  - Sierra Club, Global Warming Solutions Forum, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 40)
  - Silicon Valley Leadership Committee meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 41)
  - Society for Risk Analysis (SRA) meeting, 2006 (Box 116, Item 42-43)
  - UN Foundation, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - US Green Building Council lecture, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 45)
  - University of Wisconsin, Climate Change Conference, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 46)
  - Woods Institute for the Environment (WIE), 2006 (Box 116, Folder 47)
  - World Presidents’ Organization (WPO)/Young Presidents’ Organization (YPO), Global Warming Summit, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 48)
  - Wright Colloquium, 2006 (Box 116, Folder 49)
  - Acterra seminar, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Adelaide, Australia, 2007 (Box 117, Item 2-3)
  - Aldo Leopold Leadership Program (ALLP), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 2007 (Box 117, Item 5-6)
  - American Association of Geographers (AAG), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - American Geophysical Union (AGU), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - American Nuclear Society, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Audubon retreat and interview, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Argentina and Chile trip, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Arizona State University, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Bluth Enterprises, global warming interview, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Butler University, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - CALEPA waiver hearing, 2007 (Box 117, Item 15-16)
  - California Climate Action Registry, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - California State University, Northridge, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Carbon Offsets Workshop, Woods Institute for the Environment (WIE), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Chinese New Year, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Climate Change Policy, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - CNN International interview, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Community Involvement Leadership Roundtable, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Consumer Alternative Fuel Expo, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - Dissertations initiative for the advancement of Climate Change Research (DISCCRS) II, 2007 (Box 117, Item 25-26)
  - Eco-advice column, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - Energy and Climate Summit, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Energy Modeling Forum (EMF), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - Energy Seminar (IPCC panel), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Environment Business Australia, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - Exploratorium interview, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Family Farm Thinking Discussion, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Future Climate Change Conference, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Global Green, 2007 (Box 117, Item 36-37)
  - Good Business Network (GBN), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 39)
  - Global Green, Oscar party, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 38)
  - Google Hybrid event, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 40)
  - Grace Cathedral Summit, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 41)
  - Green Horizon documentary, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 42)
  - Gunn High School talk, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 43)
  - Greenhouse, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 1-3)
  - Haagen-Smit Symposium, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Hewlett Foundation, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - History of Climate Symposium, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - IDEO talk, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Indiana Health Advocacy, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) (Bangkok), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) (India), 2007 (Box 117, Item 10-12)
  - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) (Valencia), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Interfaith event, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - International Energy Workshop (IEW), 2007 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Journalism conference, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Leukemia and Lymphoma Society, 2007 (Box 117, Item 17-18)
  - LMI, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Marketplace Global Warming Conference, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - MIT lecture, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Michigan State University, Climate Symposium, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Monsanto, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - NASA Ames, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), annual meeting, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Climate Change Science Program, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), grant documentary, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - National Physicians Leadership Council, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - Nature Conservancy, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - PG&E talk, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - Pension Real Estate Association, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - PLAN-Boulder, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Richemont talk, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Science Teachers Association of New York State (STANYS) conference, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Science and Technology hearing, 2007 (Box 117, Item 36-37)
  - Senator Barbara Boxer, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Shared Futures/Common Ground, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Sierra Club, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Society for the Advancement of Blood Management (SABM), annual meeting, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Society of Environmental Journalists (SEJ) conference, 2007 (Box 133, Item 5-6)
  - Sonoma State University, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence for Use, National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 2007 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Steamboat Weather Summit, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Stanford in Government Panel on Climate, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Strata Decision Technology, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Sun Microsystems, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Tokyo Symposium, 2007 (Box 133, Item 13-15)
  - Tudor Investment Corporation, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists (UCS), 2007 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - UNEP briefing/ Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), press event, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - UN Security Council, conference call, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Universite Catholique de Louvain, 2007 (Box 133, Item 20-21)
  - University of San Francisco, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - University of Washington, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - VHA Council Physician Leadership, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Warren Washington Symposium - National Center for Atmospheric Research (NCAR), 2007 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Ways and Means, committee hearings, 2007 (Box 133, Item 26-27)
  - Woods Institute for the Environment (WIE), 2007 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - World Food Day, 2007 (Box 133, Item 29)
  - World Forestry Center, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - World Wildlife Fund (WWF), 2007 (Box 133, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous, 2007 (Box 133, Item 32-34)
  - Focus the Nation: various universities, 2008 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Congressional briefing, Washington, D.C., Jan. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - IOM/EPA: Decision Making Under Uncertainty, meeting 2, Washinton. D.C., Jan. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - 8th National Conference on Science, Policy and the Environment, Washington, D.C., Jan. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth College keynote at Dickey Center, Hanover, CT, Jan. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Post-Bali U.S. scientists declaration: conference call, notes, and drafts, Feb. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - IOM/EPA Uncertainty meeting 3, Washington, D.C., Feb. 2008 (Box 129, Item 7-8)
  - WWF Climate Camp, San Francisco, CA, Feb. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Clark Lecture, University of Oregon, Eugene, OR, Mar. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - NSF Roundtable, Arlington, VA, Mar. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - NAS: Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence for Use, 3rd meeting, Washington, D.C., Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Blue Planet Summit, Honolulu, HI, Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Intel Corp. presentation, Santa Clara, CA, Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Planning Institute of Australia, Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Item 15-16)
  - Future Climate Change: Learning from the IPCC FAR, Amsterdam, Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - EcoCity World Summit, San Francisco, CA, Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Item 18-19)
  - Brown is Green conference, Brown University, Providence, RI, Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - National Academy of Sciences annual meeting, Washington, D.C., Apr. 2008 (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Bing Overseas Study program 50th anniversary, Stanford, CA, May 2008 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Management Science & Engineering 453c seminar, Stanford, CA, May 2008 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - EPA visit to Stanford: Impacts of climate change on air quality, Stanford, CA, May 2008 (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - 19th annual Transportation Research Conference, University of Minnesota, St. Paul, MN, May 2008 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - USC Energy Institute Climate Change Conference, Los Angeles, CA, May 2008 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - IOM/EPA: Decision Making Under Uncertainty, 4th meeting, Chicago, IL, May 2008 (Box 129, Item 27-30)
  - MIT: Earth, Atmospheric, & Planetary Sciences 25th anniversary, Cambridge, MA, June 2008 (Box 129, Folder 31)
  - Coalition for Clean Air/CAL Air Quality Awards, Los Angeles, CA, June 2008 (Box 129, Folder 32)
  - Google/NASA Ames carbon workshop, Mt. View, CA, June 2008 (Box 129, Folder 33)
  - California Cool:Transformation to a global low carbon economy, San Francisco, CA, June 2008 (Box 129, Folder 34)
  - International Symposium: Mid-Long term strategy for climate change, Tokyo, June 2008 (Box 129, Folder 35)
  - Rothbury Think Tank festival, Rothbury, MI, July 2008 (Box 145, Item 1-3)
  - IOM/EPA Uncertainty meeting, 5th mtg., Washington, D.C., July 2008 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - CTO Forum. Energy Ingenuity: Evolution to 2030, San Ramon, CA, July 2008 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Climate change meeting with CA Attorney General Jerry Brown, San Francsco, CA, July 2008 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - American Museum of Natural History documentary filming, San Francisco, CA, July 2008 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Assisted Migration Working Group, meeting 1, Milwaukee, WI, Aug. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - ESRI Conference, San Diego,CA, Aug. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - AOU/COS/SCO meeting, Portland, OR, Aug. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Science Foo Camp at Google, Mt. View, CA, Aug. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - 6th International Congress of Artic Social Sciences (ICASS VI) Nuuk, Greenland, Aug. 2008 (Box 145, Item 12-13)
  - 5th Annual California Climate Change Conference, Sacramento, CA, Sept. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Climate Works annual meeting, Berkeley, CA, Oct. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Program on Energy & Sustainable Development, Oct. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - International Conference for a Sustainable Future, Tokyo, Nov. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - NAS: Thinking about potential catastrophes from climate change, Washington, D.C., Nov. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - Mexican Ecological Congress, Merida, Yucatan, Mexico, Nov. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Global Green USA board meeting, New York, NY, Dec. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - AGU Fall meeting, San Francisco, CA, Dec. 2008 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - Assisted Migration meeting, Santa Barbara, CA, Jan. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - IPCC workshop:Learning from the IPCC's Fourth Assessment Report (AR4), Amsterdam, Jan. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Workshop on the coastal ecosytems of CA, OR, and WA, San Francisco, CA, Jan. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - 4th annual Community Oncology Conference, Scottsdale, AZ, Feb. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - NAS Regional meeting, Irvine, CA, Feb. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - EPA Region 9 climate change speaker series, San Francisco, CA, Feb. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - "To the Point" interview on Trilliant Network, Redwood City, CA, Feb. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - League of Women Voters "Great Decisions" talk, Los Altos, CA, Mar. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - NSF/Discover/Exploratorium: Challenges of Climate Change & photo shoot, San Francisco, CA, Mar. 2009 (Box 145, Folder 30)
  - National Academies: Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence Use, 5th meeting, Paris, Mar. 2009 (Box 145, Item 31-32)
  - 15th Conference of the Parties (COP 15), Mar. 2009 (Box 145, Item 33-34)
  - Miscellaneous travel 2008 (Box 155, Item 1-39)
  - C-Roads Webinar, Palo Alto, CA, Jan. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - RCPA Pathology Update 2009 + New Zealand and Australia visits, Sydney, Australia, Mar. 2009 (Box 157, Item 2-3)
  - Blue Ocean Regional Innovation Forum, Potland, OR, Mar. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Summit on America's Climate Choices, Washington, D.C., Mar. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Turning the Tide, Fort Baker, CA, Apr. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Department of the Interior Conference on Business Opportunities in the Islands, Honolulu, HI, Apr. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Augsburg College 2009 Sverdrup Lecture, Minneapolis, MN, Apr. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - 3rd UN Foundation CEO meeting on climate, Washington, D.C., Apr. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Global Change/Global Health: Symposium on Urban Heatlh in the 21st Century, Berkeley, CA, May 2009 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Climate Crisis & Intervention, Los Altos Hills, CA, May 2009 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Stockholm meeting with Lars Erik Liljelund, Stockholm, Sweden, May 2009 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - SUM Lecture/Arne Naess Lecture/Oslo trip, Oslo, Norway, June 2009 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Ny-Alesund Symposium 2009, Svalbard, Norway, June 2009 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Hawaii Conservation Conference, Honolulu, HI, July 2009 (Box 157, Item 15-16)
  - IPCC/AR5 Scoping meeting, Venice, Italy, July 2009 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Tipping Point Productions: The Soiree, San Francisco, CA, July 2009 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - World Pension Forum, Monarch Beach, CA, Aug. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Google Archiving Meeting, Mt. View, CA, Aug. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - UCLA Climate Forum, Aug. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Arne Naess Symposium/Sustainability Summit, Oslo, Norway, Aug. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Asko meeting of the Beijer Institute, Stockholm & Asko, Sweden, Sept. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - State of the San Francisco Estuary Conference, Oakland, CA, Sept. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - Governor's Global Climate Summit 2, Los Angeles, CA, Sept. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 25)
  - National Taiwan University (NTU) talk, Taipei, Republic of China, Oct. 2009 (Box 157, Item 26-27)
  - National Academies: Standing Committee on Social Science Evidence Use 6th meeting, Washington, D.C., Oct. 2009 (Box 157, Item 28-29)
  - LSU & Loyola University visits, New Orleans, LA, Oct. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 30)
  - Business Strategies for Environmental Sustainability Program, Stanford, CA, Oct. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 31)
  - Stanford Institute for Economic Policy Research (SIEPR) forum, Stanford, CA, Oct. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 32)
  - East-West Center: Climate Change Impacts talk, Stanford, CA, Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 33)
  - "Science as a Contact Sport" media tour/NGS Fellows trip, Washington, D.C. & New York, NY, Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 34)
  - Science & Security Board (SASB) meeting, Washington, D.C., Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 35)
  - Supreme Master Ching Hai International Association TV conference, Washington, D.C., Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 36)
  - Global Green 10th Annual Sustainable Design Awards, New York, NY, Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 37)
  - "Science as a Contact Sport" book launch party, Los Angeles, CA, Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 38)
  - Yoriko for Assembly: IDEO fundraiser, Palo Alto, CA, Nov. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 39)
  - CASETRA Summit, Yaounde, Cameroon, Africa, Nov. & Dec. 2009 (Box 157, Folder 40)
  - Maymont Foundation Planet in Peril: Richmond, VA, April 1989 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - NAS 126th Annual Mtg: Symposium on Global Environmental Change: Washington D.C., April 1989 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - MIT: Energy and the Environment in the 21st Century: Cambridge, MA, March 1990 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - AAAS Annual Mtg.: New Orleans, LA, February 1990 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - American Geophysical Union (AGU) Front Range Branch Annual Mtg.: Boulder, CO, Feb 1990 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - UNC: Environmental Change and Public Health: Chapel Hill, NC, January 1990 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - UCLA: Endangered Earth Conference: Los Angeles, CA, January 1990 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - 8th Asko Meeting: Environment, Development and Trade: Asko, Sweden, September 2000 (Box 162, Folder 8)
  - IPCC/WG2 Synthesis Report Travel: Amsterdam, November 2000 (Box 162, Folder 9)
  - Visiting Professorship: Universite Catholique de Louvain: Louvain-la-Neuve, Belgium, June 12-July 3 (Box 162, Folder 10)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory: Global Climate Feebacks: Upton, NY, June 1990 (Box 162, Folder 11)
  - Interparliamentary Conference on the Global Environment: Washington D.C., April-May 1990 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Parliamentary Forum on Global Climate Change: Ottawa, Canada, April 1990 (Box 162, Folder 13)
  - IPCC/WG1/SAR Misc. Agenda, memos, travel docs: Brighton, UK, March 1994 (Box 162, Folder 14)
  - Civil Environmental Task Forum (CETF) Proposal: Washington D.C., April 1994 (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR) Workshop: Boulder, CO, April 1994 (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - North American Ornithological Conference: Missoula, MT, June 1994 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - IPCC/COP 5 meeting: Bonn, Germany, October-November 1999 (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - AAAS 2000 Annual Meeting: Washington, DC, February 2000 (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - Energy Modeling Forum Meeting on Global Climate Change: Palo Alto, CA, February 2000 (Box 162, Folder 20)
  - Disher Music and Sound: "Laboratory Earth" audiobook taping: San Francisco, CA, March 2000 (Box 162, Folder 21)